Our soul connection is so profound
that God answered all our pleas
Even your silence could tell
Everything I heard
God answered all our pleas
It is truly a blessing showered upon us
That we are now together
I am content with the love we have
…
What more can I ask for from God?
I have reached my destination
It is God’s favour upon me
that you have become my soulmate
It is truly a blessing showered upon us
that we are now together
I am content with the love we have
…
I no longer needed to rush once I had you
You are the blessing I prayed for
How do I explain my feelings any longer?
Every moment feels dreamy with you
Now all the gatherings are filled with love
That we are now together
I am content with the love we have
…
I am content with the love we have.